Guide to the Dean of Students' Office records, 1951-2007
Dean of Students' Office records, 1951-2007
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Dean of Students' Office records, 1951-2007.
37-1-855, 37-1-977, 37-1-1570, 37-1-1553
Cornell University. Dean of Students' Office.
19.9 cubic ft.
Records, reports, meeting minutes, time cards
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Administrative and organization records; files of the Student Finance Commission including minutes, Selection Committee information, information on student organizations, financial statements, Student Activities Groups accounts, Travel Committee requests, Student Government reports, and time cards. Also records of the Graduate Coordinating Commission. Also, files on the Small Living Unit Council, head residents of dormitories (including head residents' manuals), the Intersession Program on Women (1968-1969), the Housing and Dining Commission, and housing issues on campus.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Administrative and organization records; records of the Graduate Coordinating Commission; and files of the Student Finance Commission including minutes, Selection Committee information, information on student organizations, financial statements, Student Activities Groups accounts, Travel Committee requests, Student Government reports, and time cards. Also, files on the Small Living Unit Council, head residents of dormitories (including head residents' manuals), the Intersession Program on Women (1968-1969), the Housing and Dining Commission, and housing issues on campus.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Students.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Dean of Students Collection #37-1-855
  - A-D
    - A Capella Choir (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Action (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Advisor of W.S.G.A. 1st Vice Pres. (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Aesculapius (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Agassiz Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Al-Djebar (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Alhilal Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Alpha Epilson Rho (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Alpha Lambda (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Alpha Phi Alpha (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - American Society for Public Administration (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - American Society for Civil Engineers (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - American Veterans Committee, C.U. Chapter (Recog. Oct. 13, 1948 ) (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Arete (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Art Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Better Government Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Book and Bowl (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Brevity (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Buffalo Society (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cadet Officers Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - The California State Society (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Campus Chest Drive (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Campus Conference on Human Relations (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - C.A.R.E. (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Le Cercle Francais (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Channing Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Chemical Engineering Student Council (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Chi Delta (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Civil Air Patrol (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Class of 1961 (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Classics Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - College of Architecture Student Council (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Coordination Comm. for International Affairs (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell after Victory (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Almanac (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Amistad Society (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Association for the United Nations (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Association on American Indian Affairs (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Boxing Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Bridge Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Bulletin (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Camera Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Chimes Staff (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Church of Christ Fellowship (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Civil Liberties Committee (Rec. Jan. 12, 1948 ) (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Conjurors (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Der Cornell Deutsche Verein (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - The Cornell Era (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Food Technology Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Football Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Grange (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Grotto, National Speleological Society (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornellians for a Central Library (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell - In - China (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Inter-Cooperative Council (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell International Relations and Model United Nations Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Law Forum (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell League of Women Voters (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Metallurgical Society (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Observer (Sunday Newspaper) (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Officers Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Outboard Racing Association (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Philatelic Society (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Philosophy Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Political Union (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Polo and Riding Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Unlabeled Material (Cornell Review Material) (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Review (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Rocket Society (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Science Fiction Society (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Ski Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Student Branch of American Society of Agricultral Engineers (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Student Branch of Institute of Aeronautical Engineers (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Student Chapter of the American Veterinary Medical Association (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Student Extension Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Student Veterans Association (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Undergraduate German Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Undergraduate Wildlife Conservation Society (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell United Religious Work (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell University Joint Student Branch American Institute of Electrical Engineers and Institute of Radio Engineers (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell University Weightlifting Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Volleyball Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell West Indian Association (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Widow (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Cornell Wrestling Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Credo (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Unlocated (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - C.U.E. Shows (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Delta Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Delta Theta Phi (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - DLA (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Dorm Four Men's Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Dorm Nine Club (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Dorm President's Handbook, 1960-1961 (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
    - Dorm President's Handbook, 1961-1962 (Box 37-1-855 - 1)
  - E-P
    - Eagle and Anchor Society (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Epsilon Phi Sigma (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - European Students Projects Committee (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Evigol (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1947-1948 (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Fallout (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Farm Society League (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Federal Union (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Federation of American Studies (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Field Ornithology Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Finger Lakes Ski Patrol (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Food Processors Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - French Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Gamma Phi Iota (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Gargoyle (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - German Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Gilbert and Sullivan Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Government Graduate Students Coffee Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Graduate Organizations Incoming Reports (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Graduate Student Board (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Greek Orthodox Youth of America (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - The Griffith (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Hill Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Hillel Kosher Cooperative (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Hillside Cooperative (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - History Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Home Economics Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Hotel Greeters of America - Cornell Chapter (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Independent Council (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Independent Council, 1946-1949 (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Industrial and Labor Relations Commentator (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Industrial and Labor Relations Student Council (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Industrial Relations Research Association - Cornell Chapter (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Institute of Chinese Engineers (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - International Organization of Cornell University (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Inter-Protestant Council (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Iota Mu (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Ithaca Baroque Ensemble (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Ivory Tower (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Ivy Tower (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Japan - America Conference Committee (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Junior Hotel Men of America (Cornell Chapter) (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Junior Veterinary Medicine Association (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Kappa Beta Phi (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Kappa Phi Kappa (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Kappa Tau Chi (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - The Kefti (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Kermis (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Kline Road Council (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Komos Aeidein (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Kosmos - President's folder - Landmesser (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Labor School Magizine (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Labor Youth League (Cornell Chapter) (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Latin American Association (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Latin American Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Lazy Club (Horticulture Graduate Students) (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Lerion (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Magdalena River Society (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Marxist Discussion Group (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - The Math Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Men's Dormitory Social Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Men's Residence Council of Cornell University (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Mitchell Air Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Moslem Association (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Mu Sigma Tau (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Neptune Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - New Rochelle Club of Cornell (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Organizations for Candidates for National Presidents (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Organization of Cornell Planners (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Oriental Club (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Pan-American Association (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Pan-Am Tempos (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Peoples Songs of Cornell (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Pershing Rifles, 2nd Battalion (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Phi Alpha Delta (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Phi Kappa Phi (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Phi Zeta (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Phobeus (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Phi Alpha Xi (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Pi Lambda Theta (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Pi Omicron Pi (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Political Council of Cornell (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - President's Report, W.S.G.A., 1951-1952, Fraeda Aronovitz (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - Program Coordinators, 1960-1961 (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
    - W.S.G.A. Minutes, 1959-1960 (Box 37-1-855 - 2)
  - R-Y
    - Railroad Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Red Key (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Reserve Officers Association (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Rochester Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - ROTA (Legal Fraternity) (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Russian Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Saddle Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Sage Men's Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - St. Thomas More Guild - Inactive (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Scalp and Blade, Inc. (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Schafts - Inactive (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Sears Scholarship Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Semphore (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Sigma Alpha Sigma, Eta Chapter (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Sigma Xi (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Skytones - Inactive (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Social Chairman's Association (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Social Work Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Sociedad Hispana de Debate - Inactive (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Society of Automotive Engineers (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Spanish Conversation Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Speaker Series (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Activities - Student Council Cornell for Victory Committee (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Activities - Student Council Victory Chess (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Activities Center (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Agencies (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Art Guild (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Christian Movement (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Committee for a Fair Election ( 1950 ) (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Council, 1949-1951 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Council, 1958-1959 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Council Min., etc., 1956, 1957, 1958 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Council - Current (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Council Development Commission (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Council Development Commission - Minutes, 1954-1956 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Faculty Committee of Home Ec. (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Students for Democratic Action (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Students for Peace (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student League for Industrial Democracy, Cornell Chapter (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Student Zionist Organization - Inactive (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - The Travellers (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Undergraduate Biochemistry Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Undergraduate Mathematics Society (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Undergraduate Philosophy Club (Formerly Socratic Society) - Inactive (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Undergraduate Physics Society (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Undergraduate Sociology and Anthropology Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - United World Federalists (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Wayside Aftermath (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Westchester Club (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - West Essex Club of New Jersey (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Willard Straight Student Employees Association (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. House of Representatives Meetings, 1947-1948 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. House of Representatives Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. House of Representatives Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. House of Representatives Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. House of Rep. Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. House of Rep. Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. House of Rep. Minutes, 1955-1956 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. House of Rep. Minutes, 1949-1954 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. House of Rep. Minutes and General, 1954-1958 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. Annual Reports (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. Executive Committee Minutes, 1948-1949 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. Executive Committee Minutes, 1949-1950 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. Executive Committee Minutes, 1950-1951 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. Executive Committee Minutes, 1951-1952 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. Executive Committee Minutes, 1952-1953 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. Executive Committee Minutes, 1948-1953 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. Executive Committee Minutes, 1953-1957 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. General, 1951-1952 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - W.S.G.A. Treasurer, 1943-1947 (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Young Cooperators (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
    - Young Progressives of America (Box 37-1-855 - 3)
- Dean of Students Collection #37-1-977
  - American Council on Education, 1959-1961 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 1)
  - Apartments, 1955-1957 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 2)
  - Clippings, 1949; 1955,; n.d. (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 3)
  - CURW 1957-1958 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 4)
  - Day, Edmund E. (President), 1946-1949 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 5)
  - de Kiewitt, C.W. (Provost and Acting President), 1949-1951 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 6)
  - Discipline, 1938; 1950,; 1952 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 7)
  - Dormitories, 1952-1954 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 8)
  - Foreign Student Counselor, 1956; 1957 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 9)
  - F.R.J.B. Freshman Residential Judiciary Board, 1957-1959 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 10)
  - F.R.J.B. Minutes and Outline, 1958; 1959 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 11)
  - Greek Week, 1939; 1950,; 1958 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 12)
  - Land Grant Colleges, 1950-1951 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 13)
  - Land Grant Colleges, 1951-1952 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 14)
  - Male Applicants [Assistant Dean of Students], 1960 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 15)
  - Men's Judiciary Board 1953-1954 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 16)
  - Men's Judiciary Board 1954-1955 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 17)
  - Men's Judiciary Board 1955-1956 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 18)
  - Men's Judiciary Board 1956-1957 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 19)
  - Men's Judiciary Board 1957-1958 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 20)
  - Men's Judiciary Board 1958-1959 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 21)
  - NAWC - 1960 Conference [National Association of Women's Deans and Counselors], 1959 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 22)
  - Orientation, 1958-1961 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 23)
  - Proctor's Reports, 1955-1959 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 24)
  - Proctor George, 1956-1957 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 25)
  - Proctor, 1957-1958 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 26)
  - Proctor's Report - Pending, 1958 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 27)
  - Proctor's Reports, 1960; 1961 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 28)
  - Religions [LIFE Series], 1955 (Box 37-1-977 - 1, Folder 29)
  - Social Organizations and Annual Reports, 1929-1946 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 1)
  - [Student Activities], 1960-1962 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 2)
  - Student Conduct-Misc., 1946-1951 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 3)
  - Student Conduct Committee, 1947-1951 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Committee on Student Conduct 1951-1952, 1947-1951 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Committee on Student Conduct 1949-1950, 1948-1952; 1955,; 1956 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Committee on Student Conduct 1955-1956, 1951-1956 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Committee on Student Conduct 1952-1953 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Committee on Student Conduct 1953-1954, 1951-1954 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Committee on Student Conduct 1954-1955 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 10)
  - Student Conduct, Committee on, 1956-1957 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 11)
  - Student Conduct, Committee on, 1957-1958 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 12)
  - Student Conduct, Committee on, 1958-1959, 1958-1960 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 13)
  - Student Conduct Committee - Letters to Parents, 1958-1959 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 14)
  - Student Conduct Committee - Letters to Parents, 1959-1960 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 15)
  - Five Day Rule [Faculty Committee on Student Conduct], 1959; 1960 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 16)
  - Student Council Correspondence, 1955-1957 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 17)
  - Student Council (Minutes), 1950-1951 to 1955-1957, 1949-1957 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 18)
  - Student Council (Minutes), 1955-1956, 1954-1956 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 19)
  - Student Council (Minutes), 1956-1957 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 20)
  - Student Council (Minutes), 1957-1958 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 21)
  - Student Council (Minutes), 1958-1959, 1957-1959 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 22)
  - Summer Session to 1956-1957, 1948-1957 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 23)
  - Transportation, 1956-1962 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 24)
  - University Faculty, 1947-1950 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 25)
  - University Faculty, 1950-1951 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 26)
  - University Faculty, 1951-1952 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 27)
  - University Faculty, 1952-1953 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 28)
  - University Faculty, 1953-1954 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 29)
  - University Faculty, 1954-1955 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 30)
  - University Faculty, 1955-1956 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 31)
  - Willard Straight Hall, 1950-1960 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 32)
  - Women, Commission on Education of, 1954-1959, 1950-1959 (Box 37-1-977 - 2, Folder 33)
- Dean of Students Collection #37-1-1570
  - Cornell Outing Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Polo Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Parachute Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Pomology Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Poultry Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Pre-Law Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Pre-Vet Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 7)
  - Cornell Radio Guide - WVBR (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Rangers (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Savoyards (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Society of Individuals (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 11)
  - Cornell Spiked Shoe Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 12)
  - Cornell Student Branch of the I.A.S. (Institute of Aeronautical Engineering) (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 13)
  - Cornell Student Branch of the American Nuclear Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 14)
  - Cornell United Religious Works (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University Glee Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 16)
  - Cornell Widow (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 17)
  - Cornell Women's Glee Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 18)
  - Cosmopolitian Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 19)
  - Council for United Action (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 20)
  - Credo (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 21)
  - Criket Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 22)
  - Delta Sigma Rho (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 23)
  - Dialogue (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 24)
  - Engineering Council (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 25)
  - The Episcopal Church at Cornell (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 26)
  - Eta Kappa Nu (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 27)
  - Football Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 28)
  - Floriculture Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 29)
  - Grin and Grip (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 30)
  - Ho-Nun-De Kah (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 31)
  - Hotel Ezra Cornell (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 32)
  - Hotel Sales Management Program (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 33)
  - Hungarian Students (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 34)
  - Inter-Varsity Christian Fellowship (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 35)
  - Interfraternity Council (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 36)
  - Iranian Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 37)
  - Israeli Students Organization (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 38)
  - Jordani (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 39)
  - Kappa Kappa Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 40)
  - Kosmos (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 41)
  - Lutheran Student Association (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 42)
  - Majura-Nalanda (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 43)
  - Men's Independent Council (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 44)
  - Men's Glee Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 45)
  - Men's Judiciary Board (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 46)
  - Mortar Board (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 47)
  - Narmid Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 48)
  - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 49)
  - National Collegiate Players - Cornell Chapter (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 50)
  - New Freedom (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 51)
  - Notables (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 52)
  - Octagon Productions Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 53)
  - L'Ogive (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 54)
  - Omicron Nu (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 55)
  - Pak Cornellians (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 56)
  - Pan Hellenic Council (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 57)
  - Pershing Rifles (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 58)
  - Phi Beta Kappa (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 59)
  - Phi Delta Kappa (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 60)
  - Phi Delta Phi (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 61)
  - Pi Delta Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 62)
  - Pi Sigma Epsilon (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 63)
  - Pi Tau Sigma (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 64)
  - Psi Chi (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 65)
  - Pros Ops (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 66)
  - Rifle and Pistol Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 67)
  - Round Up Club (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 68)
  - The Redman (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 69)
  - Repertoire Concert Band - 1959-1960 (Mr. Romersa, Director) (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 70)
  - Rho Psi (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 71)
  - Rod and Bob/Pyramid Society (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 72)
  - Sage Chapel Choir (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 73)
  - Scabbard and Blade (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 74)
  - The Sherwoods of Cornell (Box 37-1-1570 - 3, Folder 75)